

HELLO, I'M ELVIS MUGISHA

l am a talented, ambitious and hardworking young man who is a team player but can also work independently

Confident in working with various computer systems and software configuration processes.

Comfortable in working in fast-paced environment and delivering exceptional results in a timely manner

Experienced Front-End and Back-End Developer with excellent attention to detail and problem-solving skills

Proven experience with Python. Proficient in web development techniques and creating web applications such as Python Django, JavaScript, CSS, HTML and MySQL.

Familiar with Linux and GitHub

Applying For Software Developer Role

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- Django
- Rest APIs
- AWS
- MySQL,SQL

- Apache Tomcat
- Bootstrap
- Java
- Spring Boot
- Servlet

- Rest Services
- Postgres
- HTML
- CSS

EXPERIENCE

Innov8POD Jun 2022 - Present Rwanda (Remotely)

Innov8 Incubator program

Feb 2022 - April 2022 Rwanda

Java Training Sept 2022 - Oct 2022 Rwanda

A.S.S Partners-Itd

Sept 2021-Nov 2021 Rwanda, Kigali

Personal Project

March 2022-April 2022 Rwanda

EDUCATION

Ines Ruhengeri Sept 2018 - Dec 2021

Musanze, Rwanda

St Mathieu Busasamana

Jan 2015 - Nov 2017 Rubavu, Rwanda Bachelor Degree in Software Engineering

High School Diploma in Math-Chemistry & Biology

Software Developper

Innov8POD is a start up digital transformation company located in Singapore that provide Tech Product Management Services to other businesses. We work in an agile environment to transform business ideas by brainstorming the idea or problem into solution based on client's requirements and expectations.

Tech lead

As the teck lead. I led pod of 6 team members to evaluate the needs of store managers in Rwanda conducted 25 interviews and collaborated with UX lead to design prototypes. As a result the proposed solution wasvalidated and is on the roadmap to be implemented as an MVP application

Innov8 Java Training

During this one month of training in Java we have covered so much. There was included Java basics, Servlet, Rest Services, SpringBoot and working with Postman and of course we did more than 3 project after going through all of that.

Software developer intern

For the time i spent there at ASS partners Itd i worked on so many things. Some of them are . stand-up meeting like every day and I contributed in so many things too. Such as updating the ASS Partne's Database, Updating and Testing functionality of the existing systems. I was in a team which had a huge project of developing a Software API based application for Web . Android and IOS

VisionArchitects Website

A minimalistic website aimed to perfection, the goal of creating this website was to help VisionArchitects to have a place where they can add their project so that people can see their work and contact them through the website, make comments to their work and even testify about their excellent work.

PORTFOLIO

https://elvismugisha.github.io/

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH FRENCH KINYARWANDA



HOBBIES & INTEREST



Learning new things

LEARN MORE ABOUT ME



https://github.com /ElvisMugisha?tab=repositories



https://www.linkedin.com/in/elvis-mugisha-a846b1230/



mugishaelvis104@gmail.com



+250780527973